

MOHAMMAD AL ZUIBE

FOOD& BEVERAGE MANAGER

J 00971 5555 4 2011

mohamed.zuibe@gmail.com

United Arab Emirates, Sharjah, Al Taawun Street

Nationality Jordanian

Driving LicenseAvailable upon request

SKILLS

Communication Skills

Flexibility & Adaptability

Micros & Opera Skills

Computer Skills

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

French

PROFILE

Ambition is not only a goal but also the way into developing ones' career equipped with the necessary knowledge and inspiration, I believe I can overcome any tasks given by management with timely manners as I will exceed guest expectations and provide the best quality of work, I have long experience price in Hotels &Resorts Operations and management, have worked for Luxury and sophisticated brands such as Golden sands creek hotel, St. Regis, Westin hotel, Qasr Al Sarab Resorts by Anantara, Kempinski hotels and blue fig restaurant, I had learnt true leadership through continuous hard work, working as team spirit being flexible for business demands, invest on staff and train them with high end standards in addition during past 18 years of experience in Food and beverages domain 11 years in Dubai and 6 years of hospitality management, I was always solicit to get guest and staff feedback for further improvements, Eye for details person with high expectations, maximize hotel profitability and exceed targeted numbers, controlling food cost, reduce expenses and of course maintain company assets I am willing for any new challenges as I always impose continuous success, I only can say perfect practices makes perfect.

EDUCATION

Computer Information System, Philadelphia University

Jerash, Jordan | 2004 - 2009

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Food & Beverage Manager, Golden Sands Creek Hotel

Dubai - UAE | 2021 February - 2022 October

Outlets Operation Manager, Golden Sands Hotel Apartments

Dubai - UAE | 2020 February — 2021 February

Outlets Operation Manager, St. Regis Hotel -Al Habtoor City

Dubai — UAE – Habtoor City | 2018 August - 2020 February

Restaurant Manager, St. Regis Hotel -Al Habtoor City

Dubai - UAE - Habtoor City | 2017 July - 2018 August

Asst. Outlet Manager, Westin Hotel - Al Habtoor City

Dubai - UAE - Habtoor City | 2016 April - 2017 July

Asst. Outlet Manager, Qaser Al Sarab Resorts & Spa-Anantara

Abu Dhabi - UAE | 2014 November - 2016 March

Supervisor, Kempinski Hotel MOE

Dubai - UAE | 2011 October - 2014 November

Waiter, Blue Fig Restaurant

Amman - Jordan | 2004 October - 2009 December

Food and beverages manager Feb 2021 – October 2022 Golden sands creek hotel (pre-opening) – UAE – Dubai

• I have been promoted as Food & Beverage Manager, To run the show of pre-opening five star boutique hotel, Managed total of 6 outlets, conducting staff appraisal of 30 team members, Deal with different suppliers to make sure provide goods with high quality and competitive local prices, Handling F&B operations, exceed the target suggested by management, deal with all departments to finish tasks on timely manner maintain HACCP and train the team as per brand standards, provide high level of service and evaluate the team for better improvement, work with executive chef to change/ create menus and controlling the cost work with sales and events team to increase F&B revenues, work with finance team to plan yearly budget, minimum manning with high efficiency and quality of work.

Outlets Operation Manager Golden sands hotel Apartments – UAE – Dubai

Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

• Managed total of 9 outlets, one hotel and 3 hotels apartments, conducting staff appraisal of 40 team members, schedule efficient weekly roster, reduce manning staff due low business COVID19 through clear all vacation and leave balance, create lavish set menus instead of BB/HB/FB buffet to avoid wastage due low occupancy, enforce all safety measures and standards due COVID19, Impose marketing campaign through dealing with delivery aggregators, Deal with different suppliers to make sure provide goods with high quality and competitive local prices, Handling F&B operations, exceed the target suggested by management, deal with all departments to finish tasks on timely manner maintain HACCP and train the team as per brand standards, provide high level of service and evaluate the team for better improvement, work with executive chef to change/ create menus and controlling the cost work with sales and events team to increase F&B revenues.

Outlets Operation Manager St. Regis Hotel -Al Habtoor City – UAE – Dubai

Aug 2018 - Feb 2020

• I was promoted from Restaurant manager to outlets operation manager, Managing Lepatio Restaurant and pool bar outlets with total of 15 staff through create effective duty roster where you can run the operations with minimum staff and high quality of service, deal with intoxicated guest and solve complaints in professional manner, well business plan on yearly basis especially 4 quarters marketing plan, engage the staff and guest, daily HODs meeting for well communications, create the SOPs manual books and all types of checklist for consistency, observe top/less sellers items and amend the menu accordingly, increasing F&B revenue through working with sales and events team to host events in pool area, conduct one to one meeting for each team member and monthly department meeting, control food and beverages cost through spot check and monthly inventory especially for alcohol goods, maintain HACCP and food safety, taking care of company asset through maintenance snag list, control breakage for both outlets, launch summer promotions and involve recreation team of the same.

Specialty Restaurant Manager St. Regis Hotel – UAE – Dubai

July 2017 - Aug 2018

• I was promoted from Assistant restaurant manager to Specialty Restaurant manager, Best achievement where we got the best steak house winning awards on 2108, Managing steak house operation through create efficient duty roster where you can run the operations with minimum staff and high quality of service, being visible on the floor to observe the operations with eye for details well business plan on yearly basis especially 4 quarters marketing plan, engage the staff and guest, daily HODs meeting for well communications, create the SOPs manual books and all types of checklist for consistency, observe top/less sellers items and amend the menu accordingly, increasing F&B revenue through launch up selling program for the team, conduct one to one meeting for each team member and monthly department meeting, control food and beverages cost through spot check and monthly inventory especially for alcohol goods, maintain HACCP and food safety, taking care of company asset through maintenance snag list, control breakage for both outlets, launch summer promotions and involve recreation team of the same.

Asst. Outlet Manager Westin hotel (pre-opening) – UAE – Dubai

April 2016 - July 2017

• Managed heavy all day dining operation with total of 346 seat, Train more than 22 team member conducting staff appraisal, Pre opening as Assistant restaurant manager in Westin hotel 1004 rooms, creating all SOPs and manual books, checklist and booklet, supporting and involve in setting the All day dining tables and back of house, flexible to work for all shifts including In room dining and manage the operations with high end service, train the team on job training, high details of lavish and complete buffet set up, proper opening and closing shifts, assist banquets team to host buffet breakfast, lunch and dinner for huge group, extending call courtesy for in room diners to check the feedback of the guest, doing spot check for the floors in order to guarantee clear trays/trolleys, conduct daily briefing for better communications.

Asst. Outlet Manager Nov 2014 - March 2016 Qaser Al Sarab Resorts & Spa - Anantara – UAE – Abu Dhbai

• Working as Ass. Restaurant manager in a huge resorts, Hosting confidential events for a week time, assist where business demands, conducting spot check for pre arrival villas/rooms to make sure f&b amenities and minibars are on place up to standards, checklist and booklet, Support and being involved in setting the All day dining tables and back of house, flexible to work for all shifts including In room dining and manage the operations with high end service, train the team on job training, assisting to complete buffet set up and mice and place, proper opening and closing shifts, assist banquets team to host buffet breakfast, lunch and dinner for huge group, extending call courtesy for in room diners to check the feedback of the guest, doing spot check for the floors in order to guarantee clear trays/trolleys, conduct daily briefing for better communications.

Supervisor In Room Dining Kempinski hotel mall of the emirates – UAE – Dubai

Oct 2011 - Nov 2014

First luxury hotel where I have grown my career starting waiter till reaching supervisor, I was personal butler for any Royal family/ VIP delegation, deliver complete and good temperature orders on timely manners to the guest rooms, following sequence of service as instructed, working as minibar attendant, worked as order taker and answer each and every call as instructed and up to standards of service. Consistency on each task given, Train the team accordingly, daily briefing for better communication, reporting all tasks given to my manager on daily basis, maintain daily inventory, maintain the cleanliness of designated areas, extend courtesy calls to get guest feedback, preparation of OS&Es, trolleys/trays set up communicating with FO and kitchen to deliver food amenities pre arrival. Proper opening and closing shift through updating our checklist.

REFERENCES

- Chef Abdel Cluster Executive Chef Golden sands creek hotel https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdlerazzaq-attalla-3a747998
- Mr. Ashraf Cluster Hotel Manager BM hotels & Resorts https://www.linkedin.com/in/ashraf-saleh-89757a31
- Ms. Niki Walsh Senior Director Of F&B Marketing Taste of Hilton https://www.linkedin.com/in/niki-walsh-939b2a80